http://www.stoppickingonme.com/make-peace-with-yourself-and-heal-nervous-habitual-obsessive-compulsive-skin-picking/privacy-policy/

SPOM!
Official DSM Diagnosis
About This Site
Thank You
GET HELP NOW!
Blog
SPOM!
Official DSM Diagnosis
About This Site
Thank You
GET HELP NOW!
Home > HOME > Privacy PolicyYour Privacy
Your privacy is important to us at Futura House Publishing. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. You agree to these policies by virtue of using our website in a way that leads to you providing us with personal information.
State Law & Accompanying Rights
You may have additional rights originating from State laws based on where you live. These State-based rights may augment, strengthen, or otherwise somehow compliment any privacy rights you have inherently or under Federal law. Our policy is to comply fully with the privacy policies of every jurisdiction in which we operate.
Our Commitment To Children’s Privacy
Protecting the privacy of the children is especially important. For that reason, our website will never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 18. Under our Terms of Service and Conditions of Use, children under 18 are not allowed to use our website and access our services. It is not our intention to offer products or services to minors.
Collection of Personal Information
When visiting our website, the IP address used to access our website may be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer our website, track users movement, and gather broad demographic information for internal use such as statistical assessments and website improvement. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Other information may be collected as well by Futura House Publishing, which is rather typical of most websites. For instance, the source that referred you to our website is generally known. Likewise, your duration on our website, and your destination when you leave our website can also be tracked. Other common data collected includes the type of operating system the computer you are using to access our website has. Similarly, the type of web browser is often noted. Again, this is common data collection, and helps ultimately produce a better end-user experience.
Cookies are another common internet practice. Cookies are a key means of improving user experience by allows us to customize your use of our website. Simple information is transferred to your computer to allow the content and experience at StopPickingOnMe.com to reflect your actions, preferences, and so on. You are free to make adjustments in your web browser to disable these or otherwise receive notification of cookies so you can take whatever desired action you so choose. Please understand that refusing cookies may cripple some of our website features and render some aspects useless to you.
At times, you will be fully aware of information received, as you are the direct source providing it. For instance, you may comment on a blog post, reply to an email, provide an email address, complete a survey, etc. Likewise, purchases necessarily involve collecting certain information, such as credit card information, Paypal addresses, your physical address for billing and/or shipping, phone number, etc. Refusing to provide some of this information may lead to us being unable to provide you with the products or services you’ve requested.
An example of limited access to our website is where some StopPickingOnMe.com content may be protected by a username and password. Usernames and passwords will almost always be connected with some other information related to or connected with you. This is true since much content that is protected on the internet is subscription based, often paid for. Thus, the username and password must necessarily be tied to your other account data. Usernames and passwords, by their very nature, should be kept private.
Handling of Personal Information
Note that any personal information you provide to others apart from us or our vendors is wholly optional. As an example, you might disclose something in a blog post comment. That “private” information is now “public,” and we have no control over that. In like fashion, you sharing information with any other third party not functioning as a service provider to us puts that information beyond our control and becomes subject to the policy that party has in place.
Our primary intention for collecting personal and private information from you is simply to conduct our business. We can use this internally to better serve you. Accordingly, we see no reason to share your personal information to other parties and outside interests unless you have authorized us to do so. Of course, there are instances where your information is stored with third party service providers, such as email service providers, as they provide services that are industry-leading in quality and security and are far more beneficial to our end user than attempting such services “in-house.” However, you are never required to deal with any such third party directly, they are limited in how they use your information, and they cannot sell or transfer it to others in any way.
Of course, your information does comprise part of an overall whole. This aggregate of information, by contrast, may be used to understand our overall user base. Further, we may share this information about our website visitors as a whole, not individually, with third parties for various purposes, in our sole discretion.
While we are staunch privacy advocates at Futura House Publishing, there are times when even we may be forced to abandon these ideals. Illegal activity or other serious acts or allegations could create legal liability for our website. In those cases, we reserve the right to share your information, or else may simply be compelled to do so by law. On the other hand, there may be times when we would need to share your private information in order to protect our own interests. For instance, in cases of suspected or alleged copyright infringement or other intellectual property violations, it may be necessary to share personal information.
Third Party Advertising
Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, may use cookies to serve ads on StopPickingOnMe.com. The use of cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website, including past visits, as well as other websites on the internet. To opt out of the cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, our website has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers. However, you can opt out of some, though likely not all, of these cookies in one easy location at www.networkadvertising.org/choices.
Links to Third Party Websites
We have included links on this website for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these websites may differ from our own.
Change Notice
As with any of our administrative and legal notice pages, the contents of this page can and will change over time. Accordingly, this page could read differently as of your very next visit. These changes are necessitated, and carried out by Futura House Publishing, in order to protect you and our StopPickingOnMe.com website. If this page is important to you, you should check back frequently as no other notice of changed content will be provided either before or after the change takes effect.
QUESTIONS/COMMENTS/CONCERNS
If you have any questions about the contents of this page, or simply wish to reach us for any other reason, you may do so by using our Contact information.
GET HELP NOW!
Do you truly want to stop, but can’t seem to quit?
If so, this is the book for you.
Based on leading scientific research, Stop Picking On Me is a proven plan designed to help men and women of all shapes and sizes, ages, and ethnicities deal with their ‘picky’ issues.
This is the most comprehensive life-saving book ever written on the topic. You will gain overwhelming Understanding, Answers, Courage, and Hope. Learn about what you “do” and why you do it. Learn how to eradicate breakouts, and stop your compulsion to pick.
Available on Amazon!
Share this:Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Skype (Opens in new window)Click to share on Tumblr (Opens in new window)Click to share on Telegram (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pinterest (Opens in new window)Click to share on WhatsApp (Opens in new window)Click to share on Pocket (Opens in new window)Click to share on Reddit (Opens in new window)Click to print (Opens in new window)Social
View StopPickingOnMe’s profile on FacebookView teamSPOM’s profile on TwitterView wholeway_home’s profile on InstagramView UCig4AVzVUSTbJOnhx5tZ3xA’s profile on YouTubeView 110382049733415887853’s profile on Google+
Welcome to Stop Picking On Me
This website also contains the original first edition of the book, Stop Picking On Me, written in 2004. I will continue to include it here for free.
.
However, if you would like to get ALL the latest science and healing for your condition, I have written an updated version of the book sharing all of the new lessons I have learned in the past 10+ years. It is available on Amazon.
Purchase it for yourself, OR for someone who still suffers.
SPOM on Facebook
SPOM on Facebook
HOME
READ the 2004 SPOM Book
ABOUT
Privacy Policy
Terms and Conditions
Contact
Domain Names and Website Hosting
In the past 20 years I had to do a lot of research to find good QUALITY caring service providers. Here is where I register domains:
AND here's where I host my sites:
I recommend both highly.
Please keep in touch
Please keep in touch
Tags: picking skin, picking at skin, skin picking addiction, picking at my skin, picking at your skin, stop skin picking, pathological skin picking, acne scars, pick at skin, skin pick, compulsive skin picking, csp, ocd, skin picking, skin picking disorder, neurotic excoriation, Skin Ailments, Skin Diseases, treatment alternatives for skin picking, excoriation; skin picking tips, skin picking advice; skin picking medical, skin picking 101, skin picking for beginners, skin picking for dummies, skin picking remedies, skin picking natural, skin picking cure, skin picking therapy, skin picking cures, skin picking treatment, skin picking adults, how to deal with skin picking, how to overcome skin picking, how to quit picking skin, Angela Hartlin, forever marked, Proven Tips, Definition, Signs, Symptoms of Skin Picking, Stop Skin Picking Immediately, Causes of Skin Picking, Compulsive Behavior, Skin Ailments, Skin Care, Anxieties and Phobias, Substance Abuse Recovery, Mood Disorders, Anxiety Disorders, Pain Management, Health, Fitness and Dieting, Counseling and Psychology, Psychological Pathologies, Dermatology, Alternative Medicine Healing
Follow Us
Facebook
Facebook
YouTube
Google
Twitter
Instagram
© 1996-2018 mm stratton all rights reserved. There is a possibility of text or images used on this site that belong to others. No copyright infringement is implied. These are shared to help educate readers. If you have found anything on this site that needs to be fixed, credited or removed, please contact me.
Website produced by HOMECAMP
Design and writing by meg-o-rama
Available on Amazon!
Accelerated Learning SPOM Workbook
GET HELP NOW!
